Guide to the Lloyd A. Fallers Papers 1937-1977
University of Chicago Library
- Series VI: Africa Research Materials
  The main body of this series is composed of material that Fallers collected during his years at the East African Institute of Social Research. Four subseries concern the Buganda. The first folder in Subseries 3, Buganda--General Files, containing correspondence with Mrs. Fallers, will help to orient the researcher to Fallers' Buganda material, especially in relationship to Subseries 5, Buganda--Note Cards and Subseries 6, Buganda--Maps. Subseries 3, Buganda--General Files, contains a number of noteworthy manuscripts by African authors. Subseries 4, Buganda--Leadership Study Files, contains research material (1954-1957) and is composed of field notes, genealogical material, and surveys. Finally, Subseries 7, Busoga, contains Fallers' dissertation proposal, field work report, field notes (1950-1952), and his extensive notes on government administrative documents and records of African Local Government courts in Busoga District.
  - Subseries 1: General
    - Ford Foundation, Review of African Studies in the United States, manuscripts, correspondence, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 18-19)
    - Ford Foundation, Seminar on Law and Development in Africa, International Legal Center, manuscripts, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Peace Corps, Law Training Program, African Lawyers Program, Yale University, manuscripts, notes, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Washington Center of Foreign Policy Research, Task Force on Africa, manuscripts, correspondence, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 2: Basutoland
    - Ford Foundation, Land Tenure in Basutoland 1962-1963, correspondence (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Ford Foundation, Land Tenure in Basutoland 1962-1963, memoranda, agenda, and meetings of study team (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Ford Foundation, Land Tenure in Basutoland 1962-1963, land law, documents (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Ford Foundation, Land Tenure in Basutoland 1962-1963, land law, Fallers notes (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Ford Foundation, Land Tenure in Basutoland 1962-1963, itineraries of study team in Basutoland, notes (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Ford Foundation, Land Tenure in Basutoland 1962-1963, "Dunham's Stuff on Land Reform in Basutoland, " manuscript (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Ford Foundation, Land Tenure in Basutoland 1962-1963, Final Report, drafts by Cowen, Dunham, Bentsi-Enchill and Fallers (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Ford Foundation, Land Tenure in Basutoland 1962-1963, Final Report, draft by Fallers (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Ford Foundation, Land Tenure in Basutoland 1962-1963, "Recommendations and Reflections on Some Problems..., " final report by study team, manuscript (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Ford Foundation, Land Tenure in Basutoland 1962-1963, Weisfelder, Richard F., "Basotho Monarchy, " Papers in International Studies, Africa Series No. 16, Ohio University Center for International Studies (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 3: Buganda--General Files
    - Partial list of Buganda materials, correspondence, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Questionnaires on leadership and occupations, correspondence, notes, 1954-1955 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - "Busiro in the 1880s, " maps, key to map, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Busiro villages, Fred K. Kamoga, field reports, notes, manuscripts, 1956-1957 (Box 29, Folder 4-5)
    - Ganda land law, notes, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Busiro land holdings in Buganda, photocopies, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - "Katabalwa's Villages, Buganda Land Holdings, First Mailo Land Holders, 1900+, " photocopies, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - "Extracts from the Minutes Book of the Saza and Gombolola Councils of Busiro, " typescripts, correspondence, 1942-1956 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Field diary, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Field notebook, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Tribes of the Congo, research notes, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - [Ascherson, Neil], "The History of the Uganda National Congress..., " manuscript, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Chilver, E. M., "Feudalism in the Interlacustrine Kingdoms, " East African Chiefs, ed. A. I. Richards, Chapter XVI, manuscript, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Daudi Chwa, Kabaka of Uganda, "Education, Civilization, and Fereignization [sic] in Buganda, " "Further Proposals on the Memorandum on Closer Union, " "Supplementary Memorandum on the Proposed Federation of the British East African Dependencies, " ca. 1920s (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Fearn, Hugh, "The Economic Development of Nyanta Province, " bibliography, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Kagwa, Sir Apolo, Customs of Buganda, English translation, Chapters 10, 12-15, 22-23, manuscripts, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Lemono, David, "The Masai, " manuscript, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 3-4)
    - Lemono, David, "The Masai, " photographs, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Low, Donald Anthony "Religion and Society in Buganda 1875-1900, " manuscript, ca.1955 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Luima, Martin G. and others, "The Time Has Come for Self-Government for Uganda, " manuscript, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Lwanga, P. M. K., "The Life of J. K. Miti Kabazzi, " manuscript, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Mower, Jack, "Local Government North Nyanza, " manuscript, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Mulira, Eridadi Medadi K., "The Government of the People, " manuscript, 1944 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Mulumba, Semakula, "What Governor Sir Andrew Benyamin [sic] Cohen did to Kabaka Mutesa II, " English translation, manuscript, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Musoke, D. S. K., "Buganda Nyafe (Buganda Our Mother), " manuscript, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - An Interpretation, " preface, "Colonial Policy and Tribal Rulers, " Chapter I, "Buganda 1900-1939, " Chapter II, "Buganda and the Political Development of Uganda, " Chapter III, manuscript, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Roscoe, Rev. J., Enquiry into Native Land Tenure in the Uganda Protectorate, 1906, photostat, Bodleian Library, Ms Afr. S. 17 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Zimbe, Rev. B. Musoke, The Life of Rev. B. Musoke Zimbe, english translation, manuscript (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - "Kisozi Village, 1952, " manuscript, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - "Mwanga is the Kabaka of Buganda, " Chapter XV, manuscript, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Glossaries, Chapters XIII-XIV, pp. 86-108 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Leadership volumes, outlines, correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Leadership volumes, Lloyd A. Fallers, maps, tables, charts, notes (Box 31, Folder 6-7)
    - Leadership volumes, Martin Southwold, "Leadership and the Led, " manuscript (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Leadership volumes, C. C. Wrigley, "The Changing Economic Structure, " manuscript (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Leadership volumes, "The Kinship System and Political Organization, " manuscript (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Ugandan newspapers, clippings, 1951-1966 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 4: Buganda--Leadership Study Files
    - Charts of outstanding political leaders, important chiefs of the Kabaka's, 1860-1956 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Charts of Katikkiro, important chiefs of the Kabaka, Lukiiko officials, religious leaders, S. B. K. Musoke, field reports, notes, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Charts of clergy, government bureaucrats, bibliography of publications by Uganda people, S. B. K. Musoke, correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Charts of the Amanya and Ekitongole, notes, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Kabaka Daudi Chwa, last will, chart of his children, land holdings survey (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Kabaka Mwanga II, Katikkiro and important chiefs, Y. Semindi, field reports, histories (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Political situation, A. I. Richards, field notes, powers of the Kitakkiro, kinship charts, notes, 1953-1954 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Political situation, David Apter with T. Gee, field notes, "Research Design, " manuscripts, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Succession of the Kabaka, manuscipt, notes, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Tax and education statistics, Susan Elkan, correspondence, notes, 1955-1957 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - case histories [life histories], manuscripts, notes, 1950-1956 (Box 32, Folder 8-9)
    - history, traditional and tribal, manuscripts, notes, 1955-1956 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - political structure, (b) other units and (d) current attitudes, notes, 1954-1955 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - religion, magic and myth, traditional magico-religions, manuscripts, notes, 1952-1955 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - religion, magic and myth, introduced religion, manuscripts, notes, 1954-1955 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - religion, magic and myth, syncretistic movements, "The African Greek Orthodox Church in Uganda, " manuscript, 1957 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - rural, kinship, family, manuscripts, notes, 1950-1956 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - rural, kinship, terminology, notes, 1954-1955 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - rural, kinship, behavior, notes, 1953 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - rural, kinship, lineage and clan, manuscripts, correspondence, notes, 1950-1957 (Box 33, Folder 1-2)
    - rural, kinship, inheritance and succession, notes, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - rural, political structure, local units, manuscripts, correspondence, notes, 1950-1955 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - urban, political structure, other units, manuscripts, notes, 1951-1956 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - urban, political structure, current attitudes, notes, booklets, clippings, 1953-1956 (Box 33, Folder 6-7)
    - Survey and genealogies, big land owners 1900, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Survey and genealogies, Buganda royal family, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Survey and genealogies, clan officials, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Survey and genealogies, doctors, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Survey and genealogies, editors, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Survey and genealogies, government central officials, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1-2)
    - Survey and genealogies, Kabaka's nominees, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Survey and genealogies, lawyers, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Survey and genealogies, Legico and executive council members, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Survey and genealogies, Lukiiko unofficial representatives, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 6-8)
    - Survey and genealogies, ministers, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Survey and genealogies, Muslim community leaders, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Survey and genealogies, N.A.C. clergy, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Survey and genealogies, papal honors, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Survey and genealogies, party leaders, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Survey and genealogies, protectorate government, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Survey and genealogies, Protestant clergy, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Survey and genealogies, Roman Catholic clergy, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 8-9)
    - Survey and genealogies, Saza chiefs, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Survey and genealogies, Saza chiefs, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Survey and genealogies, traders, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Survey and genealogies, miscellaneous occupations, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous notes, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 5: Buganda--Note Cards
    - Area of Senkezi, Busiro, notes, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1-3)
    - Busiro villages, notes, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 4-5)
    - Careers of Ganda leaders, biographical notes, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Landholders names to be used in conjunction with Busiro and Buddu maps, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 7-10)
    - First mairo distribution from two and under, Buddu, notes, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1-2)
    - First mairo distribution from two and under, Bugangazi, notes, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - First mairo distribution from two and under, Bugerere, notes, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - First mairo distribution from two and under, Bulemezi, notes, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 5-6)
    - Mailo allotment names to be used in conjunction with maps, A-Z, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 6: Buganda--Maps
    - Buganda Province, four maps, 1954-1956 (Drawer, Folder 1)
    - Mailo allotment, seven maps, n.d. (Drawer, Folder 2)
    - Uganda land, 54 maps, 1956 (Drawer, Folder 3-4)
    - Elite study, genealogies, n.d. (Drawer, Folder 5)
    - Busiro villages ca. 1884, map, n.d. (Tube)
  - Subseries 7: Busoga
    - Africa, maps, 1947-1955 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - "Busoga and Eastern Buganda, " maps, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Busoga correspondence, 1951-1955 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - "Statement of Proposed Ph.D. Thesis `The Power System of Busoga, '"1950 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - "Power and Status in Local Communities, " fieldwork report, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Lusoga language, word lists, linguistic exercises, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Field notes, Bulamogi County, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 7-8)
    - Field notes, Nakigo, Sabawali Sub-County, 1950-1951 (Box 40, Folder 9-11)
    - Field notes, chiefs, 1950-1954 (Box 40, Folder 12-13)
    - Field notes, genealogies, 1951-1952 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Field notes, history, attitudes to government, photographs, 1950-1951 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Field notes, homicide 1947-1956, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Field notes, homicide 1947-1956, inquests, suicide, 1951-1957 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Field notes, land, 1951 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Field notes, land cases, 1950 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Field notes, law book, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Field notes, marriage, 1951 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Field notes, marriage cases, 1949-1950 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Questionnaire, schools, 1951 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Survey, statistics, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Survey, statistics, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 1-2)
    - Survey, population, cattle, crop plantings, 1948-1950 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - British Protectorate of Uganda, gazetted personnel changes 1930-1950, notes, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - British Protectorate of Uganda, Busoga District Commissioner's circulars, land case surveys, 1951 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - British Protectorate of Uganda, Busoga District Commissioner's circulars, law statistics, notes, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - British Protectorate of Uganda, Busoga District Commissioner's circulars, Busoga District Commissioner's and Eastern Provincial Commissioner's reports 1908-1937, notes, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - British Protectorate of Uganda, Busoga District council 1937-1952, minutes, notes, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - British Protectorate of Uganda, Busoga District records, annual report, notes, 1950-1954 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - British Protectorate of Uganda, Busoga African Local Government, Bugabula County Court, records, 1950 (Box 42, Folder 10-11)
    - British Protectorate of Uganda, Busoga African Local Government, Bugabula County Court, records, 1950 (Box 43, Folder 1-3)
    - British Protectorate of Uganda, Busoga African Local Government, Bugembe, Busoga District Court, records, 1950 (Box 43, Folder 4-5)
    - British Protectorate of Uganda, Busoga African Local Government, Bulamogi County Court, records, 1949-1951 (Box 43, Folder 6-9)
    - British Protectorate of Uganda, Busoga African Local Government, Bulamogi County Court, records, 1949-1951 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - British Protectorate of Uganda, Busoga African Local Government, Nakigo, Sabawali Sub-County Court, Kigulu County, records, 1920-1923, 1949-1951 (Box 44, Folder 2-5)
- Series VII: Turkey Research Materials
  Series VII, (Boxes 44 to 46), contains Fallers research materials gathered during three periods of field research in Turkey. He completed field work in Konya during 1964 and then conducted research at Edremit in 1968-1969. This series contains Fallers' correspondence from the field in 1964, manuscripts based on his research, and manuscripts written by other social scientists. The only field research material in this series is an undated notebook containing three pages of notes.
  - Research permission, manuscripts, correspondence, passport, 1971-1972 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence from the field, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Angora, Edremit, maps, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Field notebook, 3 pages, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Occupations, note cards, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Politics, manuscript, clipping, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - World War I, bibliography, notes, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - "Chronicle of Events in Edremit, " manuscript, maps, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - A Progress Report for 1964, " manuscript, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - "`Atatürk' and Islam in Modern Turkey, " "Long-term study of a Turkish Provincial Town, " "Ziya Gökalp, " manuscripts, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - "Religion in Modern Turkey, " "Islam in a Modern Turkish City, " manuscripts, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - "Turkish Islam, " Conference on Turkish-Ottoman Studies in the United States, University of Wisconsin, manuscript, May 7-9, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 6-7)
  - Atatürk, " manuscript, memorandum, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Fallers, Lloyd A., and Margaret C. Fallers, "Sex Roles in Edremit, " "Sex Roles in Egeli, " manuscripts, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Introduction, " manuscript, outline, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - A View from the Frontier, " manuscript, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Basoglu, Hasan F., reprint, 1959 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - An Alternative Strategy, " manuscript, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Çagatay, Neset, reprint, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - A Dilemma in Turkish Politics, " manuscript, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Fisek, Nusert H., and Frederic C. Shorter, "Fertility Control in Turkey, " manuscript, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Harimi, Tahir, "Edremit Sehri, " reprint, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Iz, Fahir, reprint, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Karpat, Kemal H., "From Social Estates to Classes, From Millets to National States in the Ottoman Empire, " American Universities Field Staff Conference, Tulane University manuscript, December 11-12, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Kedourie, E., reprint, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Mardin, Serif, "Status Order, Civil Society and Subjective Culture, " Conference on Subjective Culture, Anthropos Institute, Athens, manuscript, June 12-22, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Mardin, Serif, "On the Turkish Revolution, " manuscript, reprint, 1969-1970 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Some Aspects of Their Ethnic and Cultural Background, " manuscript, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Meeker, Michael E., "Some Aspects of the Ethnic and Cultural Background of the Eastern Black Sea Turks, " manuscript, correspondence, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Meeker, Michael E., "The Great Family Aghas of Turkey (A Case of Regional Political Development in Turkey), " manuscript, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Meeker, Michael E., thesis draft, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Ethnology of the Near East, Anthropology 337, " manuscript, course outline, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Hacettepe Nüfus Etütleri Enstitüsü Bülteni, newsletters, 1968-1971 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Population News, Hacettepe Institute of Population Studies, quarterly bulletin, 1969-1971 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Population Planning News, Ministry of Health Population Planning General Directorate, quarterly bulletin, 1970-1972 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Savci, Bahri, "The Development of the Directorate of the Religious Affairs in the Republican Period, " manuscript, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Schachter, Gustav, and Bruce C. Cohen, "State Economic Enterprises in Turkish Development, " Middle East Studies Association Meeting, Denver, Colorado, manuscript, November 11-13, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Shorter, Frederic C., reprint, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Studies in Family Planning, Population Council, newsletter, March 1970 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Su, Ruhi, "Turkish Folk-Songs and Their Singers, " reprint, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Turkish Social Science Association, "Izmir in Perspective 1925-1965, " research proposal, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Yalmon, Nur, "Some Observations on Secularism in Islam or The Cultural Revolution in Turkey, " manuscript, course outline, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous, newsletters, 1967, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Edremit, map, n.d. (Drawer, Folder 6)
- Series VIII: International Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences
  Series VIII, (Boxes 47 to 50), contains information from when Fallers was the Associate Editor for Anthropology for the International Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences. This series includes editorial correspondence (1962-1969) and a collection of the manuscripts that were solicited for inclusion in the encyclopedia.
  - Editorial correspondence, 1962 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Editorial correspondence, 1963 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Editorial correspondence, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Editorial correspondence, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Editorial correspondence, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Editorial correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - A, general, 1963-1965 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Adams, Robert N., 1962-1965 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Almond, Gabriel A., n.d. (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - B, general, 1962-1967 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Banton, Michael, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Beaglehole, Ernest, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Beattie, John H. M., 1963-1964 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Benedict, Burton, 1963-1964 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Berger, Morroe, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Berreman, Gerald D., 1966 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Bidney, David, 1963-1965 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Biebuyck, Daniel, 1964-1965 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Birdwhistell, Ray L., 1963-1964 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Bowers, Faubion, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Bright, William, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - C, general, 1963-1966 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Codere, Helen, 1963-1964 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Crowley, Daniel J., 1963-1964 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - D, general, 1962-1965 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Driver, Harold E., 1963-1964 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Dumont, Louis, 1963-1965 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - E, general, 1963-1965 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Eggan, Fred, 1962-1965 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Ehrich, Robert, 1962-1964 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Eisenstadt, Shmuel N., n.d. (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Epstein, Arnold L., 1963 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - F, general, 1962-1965 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Framer, B. H., 1964-1966 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - G, general, 1962-1966 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Gebhard, Paul H., 1963 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Ginsberg, Norton S., 1963-1964 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Goodenough, Ward H., 1963-1964 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Goody, Jack K., 1963-1964 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Gulliver, Philip H., 1963 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Gumperez, John J., 1964-1965 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - H, general, 1962-1966 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Heine-Geldern, Robert, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - I, general, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - J, general, 1963-1965 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - K, general, 1964-1965 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Kruskal, William, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - L, general, 1962-1966 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Leach, Edmund R., 1963-1966 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Levine, Donald N., 1964-1965 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Lewis, Phillip H., 1964 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Lienhardt, Godfrey, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - M, general, 1962-1965 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Mair, Lucy, 1963-1964 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Malkiel, Yakov, 1964-1965 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Mayer, Adrian C., 1963-1964 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Mendelson, E. Michael, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Merriam, Alan P., 1963 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Merrill, Robert S., 1964-1966 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Metraux, Rhoda, 1965-1966 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Morris, H. S., 1963 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - N, general, 1963-1965 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Nash, Manning, 1962 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - O, general, 1962-1965 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - P, general, 1962-1965 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Passin, Herbert, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - R, general, 1963-1966 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - S, general, 1962-1966 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Sebeok, Thomas A., 1964-1965 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Shimkin, D. B., 1963-1965 (Box 50, Folder 1)